It's not gonna explode. Just keep driving.
(Penny:)Warp speed ahead, Mr. Spock.
(Sheldon:)Mr. Spock did not pilot the Enterprise.
(Sheldon:)He was the science officer.
I guarantee that if he saw the Enterprise's
"check engine" light blinking...
(Sheldon:)...he would
pull the ship over immediately.
(Penny:)Oh, God, I'm gonna lose the arm.
Oop. Red light. Release accelerator...
(Sheldon:)...and slowly apply the brake.
[SHELDON SIGHING]
(Sheldon:)Nailed it.
(Sheldon:)While we have a moment...
(Sheldon:)-...may I ask you a question?
-What?
(Sheldon:)Why do you have
the Chinese character for "soup"...
(Sheldon:)...tattooed on your right buttock?
-It's not "soup." It's "courage."
-No, it isn't.
(Sheldon:)I suppose it does take courage...
(Sheldon:)...to demonstrate
that kind of commitment to soup.
(Penny:)How did you see it?
You said you wouldn't look.